In this segment of how to cure your slice, this is an image that works for a lot of people.
When you slice the ball, this is called the heel of the club and the toe of the club.
The inside and the outside.
And if you put slice spin on the ball, the inside or heel of the club is actually getting to the ball before, it's out-racing the toe of the club, like this.
The heel is out-racing the toe.
The club face opens up and that's what puts slice spin on the ball.
But, if you could use the thought, during your swing, of getting the toe of the club or the outside of the club, before the inside or heel of the club, that is going to put, as you can see, hook spin on the ball.
It could be as simple as that.
You're only one swing thought away from hooking the ball and losing your slice and this could be it.
Get the toe of the club to get to the ball before the heel.
So when you're looking at your club at address, you're looking at that club head, no matter what you do, get that toe of the club to get to the ball before the heel.
And if you do that, you are going to put hook spin on the ball and you're not going to slice anymore.